Toggle navigation [Transpose Solutions](https://www.transposesolutions.com/index.html)

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

Last updated: January 16, 2023

* * *

> We want you to feel secure when visiting our website and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so. Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, share, use, and protect that information when you visit our website.  
>   
> By using the transposesolutions.com website, our associated websites: social.transposesolutions.com, profitmarginratio.com, math-dad.com and mobile apps hosted in Google Play Store and Microsoft Store, you [agree](https://www.transposesolutions.com/terms.html) to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Please check this policy frequently, as we may amend it from time to time to reflect changes in our services and our policies relating to customer information. Amendments will become effective at the time they are posted on our website. We will not provide notice of changes in this Privacy Policy.

* * *

What we collect
---------------

#### Personal Information:

When you visit or use our online services, we may collect personal information from or about you such as your name, contact information including email address, Demographic information such as zip code, preferences and interests when you provide such information while using our online services and where we believe it is reasonably required for ordinary business purposes.  

#### Usage and Other Information:

In addition to the personal information described above, we may collect certain information about your use of our online services. For example, we may capture the IP address of the device you use to connect to the online service, the type of operating system and browser you use, and information about the site you came from and the parts of our online service you access.

* * *

What we do with the information we gather
-----------------------------------------

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

* Complying with and enforcing applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards, contractual obligations and our policies.
* Managing your preferences.
* We may use the information to improve our products and services.
* We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

Copyright © 2023 Transpose Solutions. All rights reserved.
